claxon.com 2007-05-13

# Claxon Media

**Claxon Media's Privacy Policy**

Claxon Media's mission is to consistently exceed our visitors' expectations in terms of the products and services we provide to our clients, affiliates and web surfers by creating a customized experience for each. Claxon Media collects information about our visitors (both offline and online) so that we can provide an experience that is tailored to their preferences. Since the privacy of our visitors is of paramount importance to Claxon Media, we wish to protect it and maintain the trust of our visitors while collecting the information necessary to do this. Claxon Media is fully committed to providing information about the collection and use of personal information furnished by, or collected from, visitors while using our websites, products and services. We offer visitors the choice to decline (opt out) participation in certain services and promotional benefits provided by Claxon Media. Below is an explanation of the information we collect, how we use it, and why the use of this information will benefit our visitors' experience. 

**WEBSITES:**  
The websites owned or controlled by Claxon Media may ask for and collect personally identifiable information in order to provide a customized experience. Visitors are given notice of this request and they have the ability to choose the information they wish to share with Claxon Media. Visitors will be informed about how Claxon Media may use such information, including whether it will be shared with carefully selected third parties. In most cases, the information a visitor provides is added to our database in order for Claxon Media to provide personally tailored messages which are delivered online and offline. Visitors will always be offered the choice not to provide personally identifiable information or to have it shared with others. Please note that Claxon Media does not control and will not be responsible for the privacy policies of third party websites, including websites owned or controlled by third party owners, or websites not controlled or authorized by Claxon Media. Third party websites that are accessed through links on our websites have separate privacy and data collection practices, and security measures. We have no responsibility or liability for the practices, policies and security measures implemented by third parties on their websites. We encourage you to contact them to ask questions about their privacy practices, policies and security measures before disclosing personal information. 

Questions or comments about Claxon Media or about our privacy policy should be directed as follows:  
by e-mail: [privacy@claxon.com](mailto:privacy@claxon.com)  
by writing to us at:  
Claxon Media  
14000 Commerce Parkway  
Suite G  
Mt Laurel, NJ 08054  
Attention: Privacy 

**SECURITY:**  
We respect our visitors' privacy. Personally identifiable information can be accessed and updated by the visitor during and after the registration process with the assistance of a Claxon Media customer service representative. Security is provided concerning credit card information, names, addresses, e-mail addresses and any other personal information that visitors may provide. Although "guaranteed security" does not exist either on or off the Internet, we safeguard our visitors' personally identifiable information by using industry standard practices. Currently, our websites utilize a variety of different security measures designed to protect personally identifiable information from unauthorized access by users both inside and outside Claxon Media, including the use of 56-bit encryption based on a Class 3 Digital Certificate issued by Thawte. This allows for utilization of Secure Sockets Layer, which is a method for encrypting data. This protects confidential information - such as credit card numbers, online forms, and financial data - from loss, misuse, interception and hacking. Third party websites that are accessed through links on our websites have separate privacy and data collection practices, and security measures. We have no responsibility or liability for the practices, policies and security measures implemented by third parties on their websites. We encourage you to contact them to ask questions about their privacy practices, policies and security measures before disclosing personal information. 

Questions or comments about Claxon Media or about our privacy policy should be directed as follows:  
by e-mail: [privacy@claxon.com](mailto:privacy@claxon.com)  
by writing to us at:  
Claxon Media  
14000 Commerce Parkway  
Suite G  
Mt Laurel, NJ 08054  
Attention: Privacy 

**COOKIES AND INVISIBLE PIXELS:**  
A cookie is a very small text file that is sent to a visitor's browser from a web server and stored on the visitor's computer hard drive. It assigns the computer a unique identifier. It is essentially the visitor's identification card when s/he returns to the Claxon Media website. Cookies save visitors time because they help us to provide the visitor a customized experience without having to remind us of his/her preferences each time s/he returns to our web pages. Claxon Media cookies cannot damage visitor files, nor can they read information from the visitor's hard drive.  
Cookies help us provide our visitors with a personalized online experience in the following ways:  
\- They remember visitor names and passwords for future visits so log-in is easier and faster  
\- They ensure visitors are provided with the appropriate frames and content  
\- They ensure visitors obtain the information requested  
\- They help us deliver communications that are relevant and targeted to our visitors' interests  
Claxon Media cookies do not follow visitors when traveling on the Internet after leaving Claxon Media websites. We track the usage of our websites in order to modify it according to our visitors' needs. We pay attention to what information is requested and attempt to make it easier to find such information in the future.  
If visitors do not want the benefits of these cookies they can set their browser to reject the cookies. Visitors should consult the instructions for their particular browser on how to do this. However, visitors should understand that rejecting cookies might affect their ability to perform certain transactions on our websites and our ability to recognize their browser from one visit to the next.  
Claxon Media also uses invisible pixels, sometimes called web beacons, to count how many people visit certain web pages or how ads are displayed. Information collected from invisible pixels is used and reported in the aggregate without personally identifiable information. Claxon Media may use this information to improve marketing programs and content. 

Questions or comments about Claxon Media or about our privacy policy should be directed as follows:  
by e-mail: [privacy@claxon.com](mailto:privacy@claxon.com)  
by writing to us at:  
Claxon Media  
14000 Commerce Parkway  
Suite G  
Mt Laurel, NJ 08054  
Attention: Privacy 

**EMAIL:**  
From time to time, Claxon Media asks visitors for their email address in order to provide relevant information or special offers. Email addresses may be joined with other information provided at our website and may also be augmented with other data sources. By providing their email address to us, visitors may receive email. Visitors will always have the ability to accept or decline email communications from Claxon Media. Email communication is sent only to people who have consented to receive email from Claxon Media or by our carefully selected third parties. At the time of email capture, Claxon Media will advise the visitor that we will use the email address for service and product information, as well as marketing and promotional communications. At any time a visitor may opt-out of receiving email communication by following the directions posted in every email, or by following the directions at Claxon Media's website or by contacting a Claxon Media customer service representative to opt out of email communication. Visitors may receive periodic offers and information from Claxon Media about our products and services, as well as offers and information from Claxon Media's carefully selected marketing partners. Visitors may also receive offers and information directly from these selected third parties. Visitors who do not want to receive marketing information from Claxon Media and/or these third parties in the future, have the option to contact us in order to decline such communication. 

Claxon Media offers our visitors the option to decline these communications. Visitors may contact us to opt-out of such communications as follows:  
by e-mail: [claxon@claxon.com](mailto:claxon@claxon.com)  
by phone: 1-856-642-0130  
by writing to us at: Claxon Media  
14000 Commerce Parkway  
Suite G  
Mt Laurel, NJ 08054

Once a visitor has opted out, they can choose to opt-in again by changing their profile online or by contacting us in any of the above ways. In cases when a visitor voluntarily provides personal information in response to an email (a survey or purchase form, for example, Claxon Media (or a third party engaged by Claxon Media) will inform the visitor how this information will be used. For example, information may be used so visitors can receive the goods, services or information that was requested. Claxon Media may also use this information in aggregate form to get a better understanding of the type of individuals responding to specific offers. 

**DIRECT MAIL / OUTBOUND TELEMARKETING:**  
As part of the service that Claxon Media provides its visitors, Claxon Media may mail or call its visitors to inform them of enhancements, changes in offerings, special events, or other relevant information responsive to the visitors' interests. Visitors who supply Claxon Media with their postal address or telephone number may receive periodic mailings or phone calls from us with information on new Claxon Media products and services or upcoming Claxon Media special offers/events. They may also receive mailings/calls from our carefully selected third parties.  
Claxon Media offers our visitors the option to decline these communications. 

Visitors may contact us to opt-out of such communications as follows: by e-mail: [privacy@claxon.com](mailto:privacy@claxon.com)  
by writing to us at:  
Claxon Media  
14000 Commerce Parkway  
Suite G  
Mt Laurel, NJ 08054  
Attention: Privacy 

**SWEEPSTAKES / CONTESTS:**  
Sometimes Claxon Media runs sweepstakes and contests. We ask people who participate to give us their contact information (like their email address). If a visitor participates in a sweepstakes or contest, his/her contact information may be used to reach him/her in connection with the sweepstakes or contest, and for other promotional, marketing and business purposes.  
All Claxon Media sweepstakes/contests entry forms will provide a way for participants to opt-out of any communication from the sweepstake's/contest's manager that is not related to awarding prizes for the sweepstake/contest. Entry forms will further provide contestants with a choice whether to receive email marketing materials from our carefully selected third parties. When a visitor enters a Claxon Media sweepstakes/contest, the information the visitor provides is not shared with any third party, unless the visitor agrees to such by checking the opt-in box on the sweepstakes/contest entry form. By accepting the prize, the winner agrees that Claxon Media (and those acting under its authority) may use the winner's name, picture/portrait, likeness and/or voice for advertising and other promotional purposes without further consideration, unless prohibited by law. 

Questions or comments about Claxon Media or about our privacy policy should be directed as follows: by e-mail: [privacy@claxon.com](mailto:privacy@claxon.com) by writing to us at:  
Claxon Media  
14000 Commerce Parkway  
Suite G  
Mt Laurel, NJ 08054  
Attention: Privacy 

**RESEARCH:**  
From time to time Claxon Media may perform research (online and offline) via surveys. All survey responses are voluntary, and the information collected will only be used for research and reporting purposes, to help Claxon Media to better serve its visitors by learning more about their needs. The survey responses may also be used to determine the effectiveness of our websites, various types of communications, advertising campaigns, and/or promotional activities.  
If a visitor participates in a survey, the information given by the visitor will be used along with that of other study participants (for example, Claxon Media might report that 50% of a survey's respondents are women). Claxon Media may share anonymous individual and aggregate data for research and analysis purposes.  
Claxon Media may also contact participants through e-mail for other purposes if given permission to do so. For example, if participants indicate in the survey that they wish to join a Claxon Media online research panel. When a participant submits a survey, the e-mail address and the response to the "future contact" question described above, are automatically stored in a database that is intentionally separated from the participant's survey responses. Therefore, the participant's e-mail address is not tied back to the survey responses. Claxon Media will not share with third parties the personally identifiable information provided by a survey participant in response to survey questions. For all other purposes, only aggregate data that is devoid of all personally identifiable information will be used.  
In the course of providing surveys to visitors, a cookie may be placed on their browser in order to control the research process, primarily to stop people from being asked to take the same survey twice - or being allowed to take the same survey twice. In addition, the types of advertising visitors view in emails received or on websites during the course of their web surfing, may be connected to the visitor's anonymous survey responses.  
Participation in Claxon Media's surveys is voluntary. Participants who do not wish to receive email communications from Claxon Media may opt out of the receipt of such communication by notifying us as provided below. 

Questions or comments about Claxon Media or about our privacy policy should be directed as follows:  
by e-mail: [privacy@claxon.com](mailto:privacy@claxon.com)  
by writing to us at:  
Claxon Media  
14000 Commerce Parkway  
Suite G  
Mt Laurel, NJ 08054  
Attention: Privacy 

**PERIODIC REVIEW AND MODIFICATIONS:**  
The effective date of this privacy policy is August, 2004. Claxon Media recommends that visitors review this Privacy Statement periodically, as Claxon Media may revise it from time to time.
